Finding Aid for Guild House records 1924-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Honduras Reunion, Board Meeting, and Tarps Away Photographs 2005, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 9)
  - People (identified) circa 1950s-1960s (Box 9)
  - People (unidentified) circa 1950s-1960s, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous circa 1950s-1960s (Box 9)
  - Nature circa 1950s-1960s (Box 9)
- Scrapbooks
  Scrapbooks, the seventh series, contains nine scrapbooks. The scrapbooks date from 1938 to 1966 and primarily contain photographs and ephemera related to Guild House activities and members.
  - "Mr. and Mrs. Pick with appreciation for your ministry.," Memorial Christian Church 1966 (Box 9)
  - Picks Postbox, Contents of Scrapbook 1957 (Box 9)
  - Disciples Guild Yearbook 1936-1940 (Volume 1)
  - Congregational Disciples Guild Snap & Scraps 1946-1947 (Volume 2)
  - Congregational Disciples Guild 1948-1949 (Volume 3)
  - Guild 1949-1950 (Volume 4)
  - The Congregational and Disciples Guild Yearbook 1956-1957 (Volume 5)
  - Congregational and Disciples Guild Yearbook 1957-1959 (Volume 6)
- Sound Recordings
  The final series, Sound Recordings, contains a series of reel-to-reel audio tapes. These include a conference on the Vietnam War sponsored by Guild House and sermons, as well as 18 unlabeled tapes.
  - Unlabeled, 14 tapes 7 in. reel-to-reel audio tapes (Box 10)
  - Unlabeled, 3 tapes 5 in. reel-to-reel audio tapes (Box 10)
  - Unlabeled, 1 tapes 4 in. reel-to-reel audio tapes (Box 10)
  - Conference on Vietnam, 9 tapes 7 in. reel-to-reel audio tapes (Box 10)
  - Sermons, 4 tapes 7 in. reel-to-reel audio tapes (Box 10)